Admin: 

1. View categories detail: 
 + Administrator view detail information of categories by click to name link at Manage categories page: "Click to name link la y gi Hung nhi?"
 
2. Delete categories:
 + Redirect back to --> Redirect to
 + "Logged into the system with admin role and open Category Detail page" --> Them successfully nhe.

3. Create new category:
 + "Logged into the system with admin role and go to Admin page" --> Them successfully nhaz boy. 

4. Edit Category
 + Logged into the system with admin role and open Category Detail page --> Them successfully nhaz boy. 
 + Exception - Step 3: "Leave required fields blank and click "Save" button" --> click to "Save" button

5. Add a city details:
 + Redirect to Add new city page  --> Redirect to "Add new city" page
 + 

6. Edit a city, add a district, Edit a district:
 + Redirect to Edit city page --> Redirect to "Edit city" page  
 + Luu y ten cac Page minh nen de trong qoutes nhe. 

7. Delete a city

Post-conditions
Stay remains at Manage City page  and selected city will be deleted from city list --> Stay remaining nha boy

8. List payments, List all moderator, create new moderator, Delete moderator, Edit moderator:
 + "Logged into the system with admin role and go to Admin page" --> Them successfully nha boy
 + "Admin logged in to Admin Control Panel" --> Them successfully nha boy
 + "Logged into the system with admin role and go to Admin page"  --> Them successfully nha boy
 + Name of Page thi nen cho vao qoutes nhe, ca name of button nua nhaz. 
 + "Logged into the system with admin role and open User Detail page" --> Them successfully nha boy
 + "Logged into the system with admin role and open User Detail page" --> Them successfully nha boy

9. View detail of payments: 
 + "This usecase allow admin to view detail of SMS payment" --> Cai Brieft Description nay minh chua hieu? SMS o day la ntn a
 +

User:
1. Login, Edit user profile:
 + Exceptions: Mesage --> Message nhe. 
 + 
2. Logout: 
 + "User had already logged into system" --> Them successfully nhe

3. Filter seach result
 + Loi syntax nhe. Seach --> Search (ca o phan Pre-conditions nua nhe)
 + 

4. Compare house: Error nhe
 + Exceptions: Display error message "Bạn vui lòng chọn ít nhất 2 bài đăng để bắt đầu so sánh."
--> Em nghi la minh chi so sanh 2 bai vs nhau thoi nen popup nen de message la :" Bạn vui lòng chọn 2 bài đăng để bắt đầu so sánh"

5. Delete post:
 + "RegisteredUser had logged into system and in Manage Post page" --> Them successfully nhe.

6. Renew post: 
 + Viet detail va de hieu hon nhe, em doc ma van chua hieu ro a. Em cam on.
